mathantics.com 2019-07-07

# Math Antics | Math Video Lessons for Free plus more

This Privacy Policy explains our policy regarding the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information by Math Plus Motion LLC ("we", "us"). As we update and expand our services, this policy may change, so please refer back to it periodically. By accessing the Math Antics Site ("Site") you consent to these policies.

## Collection and Use of Information

Personal information means information that can be used to identify and contact you, specifically your name and e-mail address.

When you create an account on our Site, we ask you to supply us with personal information so that we can communicate with you regarding your account. With your permission we also use your e-mail address to send you newsletters, as well as messages about Math Antics special offers, promotional announcements and consumer surveys.

We keep track of your interactions with us, including but not limited to your site activity. We use this information for such purposes as enhancing our service offering for our customers.

While using the Math Antics Site, you will have opportunities to post comments that are viewable by the public. Please understand that when you post such information, it is not subject to this policy, and you should not include personal information in any publicly viewable posts.

## Links to Other Sites

The Math Antics Site contains links to sites operated by third parties whose policies regarding the handling of personal information may differ from ours. While we endeavor to associate with reputable sites, we cannot be responsible for the information handling practices of these other sites.

## Children

You must be 13 years of age or older to subscribe to the Math Antics Site. While individuals under the age of 13 may utilize the service, they may do so only with the involvement of a responsible adult who agrees to our Terms of Use. While we do have content that may be watched by children, we do not intentionally collect information from individuals 13 years of age and younger.

## Cookies

When you log in to your Math Antics account, if you select "Remember Me", cookies are placed on your computer's hard drive. (Cookies are small pieces of data that are sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your hard drive for record keeping purposes.) The cookies will store enough information to automatically log you in to your account the next time you visit the Site. If your browser is set to not accept cookies, you will not be able to use this feature.

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on your prior visits to the Math Antics Site.

Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to you based on your visit to Math Antics and/or other sites on the Internet.

You may opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative [opt-out page](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

## Disclosure of Personal Information

We will not sell, rent or disclose your personal information to third parties.

In the event that Math Antics is acquired by or merged with a third party, we reserve the right to sell or otherwise transfer the personal information we have collected as part of that transaction. If the third party has a different privacy policy than ours, we will notify you in advance and give you an opportunity to prevent your personal information from being shared.

## Security

We take information security very seriously and use reasonable administrative, technical and managerial measures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access. For example, we only store your password in encrypted form.

You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account information and for restricting access to your computer or mobile device through which you access your Math Antics account. Users of public or shared computers or unprotected mobile devices should log out at the completion of each visit to the Math Antics Site.

Unfortunately, no security system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Accordingly, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information and cannot assume liability for improper access to it. By using this Site, or providing personal information to us through any means, you agree that we can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues relating to your use of this site.

## Changes to This Policy

As we update and expand our services, we may make changes to this policy. You should check back for updates to this policy from time to time. If the changes result in materially less protection for your personal information than that provided in this policy, we will make reasonable efforts to contact you and obtain your consent to the changes. Your use of the Math Antics Site or continued use of our service after our efforts to contact you means that you agree to be bound by such changes.

## Contact

If you have questions concerning this privacy policy, please contact us at [questions@mathantics.com](mailto:questions@mathantics.com?subject=Math%20Antics%20Question) .

Last updated: January 2011
